A Guide to the L.F. Payne, Jr. Papers, 1988-1997
Library of Virginia
- Series VI. Campaign Files, 1992-1997., Extent: 33 boxes. (Box 50-82)
  - Children's Health. (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Christmas (Donor/Contact List). (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - COC/NFIB. (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Community College Presidents. (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Contributions Over $5000. (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Coordinated Campaign Plan. (Box 56, Folder 4-7)
  - Core Group Call List. (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence. (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Coughlin, Moira. (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Cox, Doug. (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Danville. (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Dead Call Sheets. (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Debate Prep. (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Debate Requests. (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - DeFrancia. (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Democratic Caucus Campaign Workbook (Virginia), 1995. (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Democratic Lists. (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia - Central and Steering Committee Members, 1993-1997. (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Deposits, Thru 17 March 1997. (Box 57, Folder 1-6)
  - Deposits, 19 March - 2 June 1997. (Box 57, Folder 7-12)
  - Deposits, 4 June - 4 September 1997. (Box 58, Folder 1-8)
  - Deposits, 5 September - 21 October 1997. (Box 58, Folder 9-11)
  - Deposits, 5 September - 21 October 1997. (Box 59, Folder 1-5)
  - Deposits, 22 October - 5 November 1997. (Box 59, Folder 6-8)
  - Dewberry and Davis List. (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Dewberry, Sidney O.. (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - District Callbook - Charlottesville/Albemarle. (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Bill Dolan. (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Dolan Financial Reports. (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Donor Updates. (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Donors. (Box 60, Folder 2-6)
  - Dwoskin - Bad. (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Dwoskin Reception, 17 June 1997. (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Easter, Peter. (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Economic Development. (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Economic Development and Environmental Protection. (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Education. (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Education - Contacts. (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - El Sol Communications Interview, 25 April 1997. (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Election Results, 1993. (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Election Results, 1994. (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Emily's List Guides and Manuals 1994. (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Endorsements, 1994. (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Environment. (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Environment/Out of State Trash 1994. (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Exchange Center Lease. (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Fairfax County Democratic Committee Breakfast, 16 May 1996. (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Farm Bureau - Ag Initiative. (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Farmington Country Club Membership Directory. (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - FCDC Mailing. (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Fifth District Lists. (Box 61, Folder 10-12)
  - Filing Deadlines. (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Finance Committee. (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Finance Staff Meeting, 2 June 1997. (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Financial Report, November 1997. (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Financial Reports. (Box 62, Folder 1-11)
  - Judith Fox/Ed Askell Reception, 1 April 1997. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Fraternal Order of Police. (Box 63, Folder 2-3)
  - Friends of Coleman Andrews - Financial Reports 1994. (Box 63, Folder 4-6)
  - Fundraising. (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising Events in Northern Virginia. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising - High Priority. (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Fundraising - High Priority. (Box 64, Folder 1-2)
  - Fundraising List - By District. (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising - Meeting Notes. (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising - NOVA. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising, October 1997. (Box 64, Folder 6-7)
  - Fundraising Plans. (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising Projections. (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Fundraising - Richmond. (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Fundraising - September. (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Fundraising - Southwest Virginia. (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Gas Tax and Sales Tax Legislation. (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - General Election Results - U.S. Senate (Virginia), 1996. (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Gibb, Barbara. (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Gilliam/Blaine. (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Goode, David. (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Gore. (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Gore Follow-up. (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - GOTV. (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Gould, Diane. (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Greater Washington Board of Trade. (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Green, Bob - VMI. (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Greer - Media Training. (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Griffin, Frederick G. - Airport Telecommunciations. (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Guest Register. (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Gun Owners of America. (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Guns/NRA. (Box 65, Folder 17-18)
  - Hager. (Box 66, Folder 1-5)
  - John Hager - Civil Rights. (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Hager Financial Reports. (Box 66, Folder 7-12)
  - Hager - Nicotine. (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Halifax (Chris Lumsden). (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Halifax County Alliance for the Mentally Ill. (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Hampton Roads Information. (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Harrisonburg. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Health Reform - General Information. (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - "Higher Education Support for Economic Development in Virginia" by Alan G. Merten, George Mason University. (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - House Democratic Caucus - Issues. (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Housing - Contacts. (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Hunt, Robert H.. (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Insurance - Contacts. (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Internet. (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Internships. (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Invite List, 18 December 1996. (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Issue Letters. (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Issues, 1994. (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Issues and Thematic Opinion Research by Penn, Schoen, and Berland Associates. (Box 67, Folder 16-19)
  - James River Association - Annual Report, 1995-1996. (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - "Juvenile Murder in Virginia". (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Kirtley, Bruce - Luncheon, 10 September 1997. (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Kirtley for Delegate, 1997. (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Labor Questionnaire. (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Lake Gaston Issue. (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Legislation - 104th. (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Lists - UVA. (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Low, Jim. (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Lynchburg. (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Martin, Phyllis - Net Schools. (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Martinsville Campaign Event. (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - McLean Luncheon, 30 September 1997. (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Media Planning Budget, 1996. (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Media Planning Guide - Virginia Lt. Governor Election. (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Media Training. (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Members of Congress. (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Minority Issues. (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - The Mix. (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Moton School. (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Murray, Bunny - Reception, 21 September 1997. (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Murray, Meghan. (Box 69, Folder 3-6)
  - National Education Association Questionnaire, 1994. (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - National Right to Work. (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Nelson County. (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Newport News Debate, 31 October 1997. (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Newsletter. (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Newsletters. (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers. (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Norfolk Shipbuilding. (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Northern Virginia - Copies of Letters Sent. (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Northern Virginia - Names That Could Be Helpful. (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Northern Virginia Roundtable. (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - NOVA Lists. (Box 70, Folder 1-3)
  - NOVA Mailing. (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - NOVA Senators News Conference, 30 October 1997. (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - "An Overview of the Commonwealth's Budget," 24 September 1996. (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - PAC's. (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Parental Notification. (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Parkinson, Len. (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Payne/Beyer/Dolan in the Press. (Box 70, Folder 10-11)
  - Payne Research Report - Part 1 of 2, May 1997. (Box 70, Folder 12-13)
  - Payne Research Report - Part 2 of 2, May 1997. (Box 70, Folder 14-15)
  - Payne Research Report - Background Materials, Book One. (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Payne Research Report - Background Materials, Book Two. (Box 71, Folder 2-3)
  - Payne Research Report - Background Materials, Book Three. (Box 71, Folder 4-5)
  - Payne Research Report - Background Materials, Book Four. (Box 71, Folder 6-7)
  - Payne Research Report - Background Materials, Book Five. (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Payne Research Report - Background Materials, Book Six. (Box 72, Folder 2-3)
  - Payne Research Report - Background Materials, Book Seven. (Box 72, Folder 4-5)
  - Susan Payne. (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Peninsula Water. (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Personal Property Tax. (Box 72, Folder 8-9)
  - Persuasion Phone Calls. (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Pfiesteria. (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Pharmacists - Contacts. (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Phone. (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Phone Messages, 7 July - 30 October 1997. (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Phone Records. (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Physicians - Contacts. (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Pittsylvania County Fundraiser, 21 August 1992. (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Policy Ideas. (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Policy Info.. (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Poll/Message Development. (Box 73, Folder 7-8)
  - Polling Info.. (Box 73, Folder 9-11)
  - Poplar Forest. (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Post-Election Analysis, 1994. (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Press Corps List - Virginia. (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Principal Registration List, 1 May 1996 - 24 January 1997. (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Pro-Business Profile. (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Prospective Donors (A-C). (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Prospective Donors (D-G). (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Prospective Donors (H-L). (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Prospective Donors (M-R). (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Prospective Donors (S-Z). (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Prospects. (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Protogyrou, Andy. (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Public Opinion Survey Results. (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Q and A, Talking Points. (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Questionnaires. (Box 74, Folder 12-13)
  - Questionnaires. (Box 75, Folder 1-3)
  - Quick Search of Interest Groups LFXMAS, 8 November 1995. (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Radio Shows. (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Radio Talk Shows. (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Realtors. (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Receipts and Disbursements, 1995-1996. (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Reimbursements. (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Remarks - 4th and 7th District Conventions. (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Remittance Envelopes. (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Report to the People - Gov. Jim Hunt, 1996. (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Resolicitations. (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Retirement Letters. (Box 75, Folder 14-15)
  - Retirement Letters. (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Right to Work/Labor. (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Roanoke River Basin Association Luncheon, 22 February 1997. (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Robb Event, 23 October 1997. (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Sabato Analysis - 1993 General Election for Governor. (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Sabato Analysis - 1995 Elections for the Virginia General Assembly. (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Saliba, Nila J., 1994. (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Saunders, Gordon F.. (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Savings and Loans - Contacts. (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Schedule, February - April 1997. (Box 76, Folder 10-12)
  - Schedule, May 1997. (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Schedule, June 1997. (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Schedule, July 1997. (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Schedule, August 1997. (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Schedule (Susan Payne), July - August 1997. (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Schedule (Susan Payne), September 1997. (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Schedule (Susan Payne), October - November 1997. (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Senate Caucus. (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Sheras, Peter. (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Sierra Club Survey. (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Signage. (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Sinsheimer Group. (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Small Business. (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Small Business. (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - "Smart Start" Program. (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Stephen - Virginia Beach. (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Social Security, 1994. (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - South Tidewater Association of Ship Repairers. (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Southern Virginia Mental Health Institute. (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Southwest Virginia Higher Education Center. (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Speech - Rockbridge County, 1996. (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Speech - State Democratic Convention, 10 May 1997. (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Staff Calls. (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Stuart, VA - Reception, 4 October 1997. (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - "A Tax Reform Agenda for Virginia" by Dean Stansel. (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Telecommunications - Bell Atlantic. (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Telephone Contract Proposals. (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Textiles - Contacts. (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Thank You's (Letters of Praise). (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Thomaidis, Irene. (Box 79, Folder 2-3)
  - Thomas Jefferson Institute for Public Policy. (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Tidewater. (Box 79, Folder 5-6)
  - Tidewater Lists. (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Tobacco - Contacts. (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Tobacco Letter. (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Tobacco Settlement. (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Transportation. (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Unions - Fifth District. (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Vendrick, Baxter. (Box 79, Folder 13-14)
  - Vendrick, Baxter. (Box 80, Folder 1-2)
  - Via, Peter. (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Aggregates Association. (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Area Health Education Centers 1996-97 Progress Report. (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Cooperative Extension Service - Mined Lands. (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Health Care Association Legislative Conference, 12 February 1997. (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Medical Political Action Committee (VAMPAC). (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Oil and Gas. (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - "Virginia Outlook" - Bureau of Business Research of the College of William and Mary, Vol. 1, no. 4 (May 1997). (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Virignia Road and Transportation Builders Association, 27 March 1997. (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Values Initiative. (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Voter Statistics. (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Youth Violence Project. (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Virginians for Payne. (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Virginians for Payne, 1994. (Box 81, Folder 2-3)
  - Virginia's Budget. (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - "Virginia's Economy and Historic Preservation". (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - VMI Class of 1967 30th Reunion Booklet. (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - VMI Database. (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Washburn, Joan. (Box 81, Folder 8-9)
  - "Water Supply in the Virginia Coalfield Counties". (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Wendell Ford Event, 9 October 1997. (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Western Transportation Corridor. (Box 82, Folder 1-2)
  - Wintergreen - Childs Lawsuit. (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Wintergreen Event, 22 June 1997. (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Women for L.F. Payne. (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Workforce Development. (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Yates, Raven. (Box 82, Folder 8-9)
- Series VII. Special Media, 1988-1997., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 83-84)
  The special media include cassette tapes, computer floppy discs, and VHS videotapes. The cassette tapes contain campaign radio spots as well as interviews by Payne and others on local radio stations. The videotapes are mostly related to Payne's campaigns for Congress and lieutenant governor, including television commercials prepared by political consulting firms, as well as coverage of debates, local news spots, and appearances. There are also short local news segments containing interviews with Payne where he shares his views on various topics and events, including Medicare, Iraq and the Mideast, education, NAFTA, tobacco legislation, and the federal budget deficit. The files contained on computer floppy discs have been reproduced in hard copy. They relate to Payne's campaign for lieutenant governor, and include staff memorandums, form letters, speeches, and fundraising information.
  - Cassette Tape - Payne for Congress (Strother, Duffy) "NRA," 1994. (Box 83)
  - Cassette Tape - Payne for Congress (Strother, Duffy) "Way of Life," 1994. (Box 83)
  - Cassette Tape - Payne for Congress (Strother, Duffy) "Way of Life Also," 1994. (Box 83)
  - Cassette Tape - Payne for Congress (Strother, Duffy) "Hey George" and "Independent," 1994. (Box 83)
  - Cassette Tape - "Eye of the Community" with George Landrith, WDVA 1250AM, Danville, 6 August 1994. (Box 83)
  - Cassette Tape - L.F. Payne, 30 August 1994. (Box 83)
  - Cassette Tape - "The Doug Wilder Show" with LF Payne, WRVA Richmond, 22 May 1995. (Box 83)
  - Cassette Tape - Tobacco News Conference, 14 July 1995. (Box 83)
  - Cassette Tape - L.F. Payne Interview, WVTF, 30 January 1996. (Box 83)
  - Cassette Tape - Coleman Andrews, 11 February 1997. (Box 83)
  - Cassette Tape - L.F. Payne for Lt. Governor (Greer, Margolis) "Leadership," "The One," and "Man of the Year",. (Box 83)
  - Cassette Tape - Payne for Congress, "Saipan". (Box 83)
  - Cassette Tape - unidentified. (Box 83)
  - Cassette Tape - unidentified (minicassette). (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne Announces Campaign for Congress, 16 February 1988. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne on Medicare (Local News Spot), L.F. Payne - Linda Arey Debate with Sharon Collins, WSET Lynchburg Channel 13, 23 May 1988. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne - Linda Arey Debate, 1988. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne - Linda Arey Debate, 4 June 1988. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - Payne for Congress Rally/Gov. Baliles, Campaign Commercial, Bush Danville Appearance for Arey (various news broadcasts), 11-12 June 1988. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne Campaign Commercials, 1988. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Congress (Fenn & King) "400 Jobs" and "Results," 1988. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Congress (Fenn & King) "Jobs" and "Results," 1988. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Congress (Fenn & King) "Jobs," 1988. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Congress (Fenn & King) "Compare," "Remember," and "Remember 2," 1988. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - Bluestone Senior High School Commencement, Chase City, 10 June 1989. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - Grand Opening of Rep. Payne's Office, Nellysford, 11 August 1989. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne on Iraqi Refugees, WVIR Charlottesville Channel 29, 23 April 1991. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne Mideast Trip, Iraq Troop Withdrawals, Refugees (Nashville speech via video), 25 September 1991. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne on Mideast Trip, Iraq Troop Withdrawals, Refugees (excerpts), WSET Lynchburg Channel 13 News, 25 September 1991. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - "Arctic Oil, Arctic Refuge," Congressional Research Service, September 1991, and ANWR Panel Discussion, House Floor Proceedings on Tax Cuts/Big Government (not LFP), Clinton Oval Office speech (part) on his economic program and Sen. Dole response, 3 August 1993. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - "Town Meeting" with Mayor M.W. Thornhill, Jr., Lynchburg Cablevision Channel 6, 1991. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - Lynchburg Cablevision Town Meeting with L.F. Payne, 21 January 1992. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - Gennifer Flowers Interview, "A Current Affair," February 1992. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - George Washington High School, Danville, 21 February 1992. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne Speech Rehearsal (Three Copies), 17 March 1992. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne Practicing at Golf Driving Range, 20-21 June 1992. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - Rep. Payne on Education, 11 August 1992. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - "Blue Ridge Nightline," Blue Ridge Public TV, Roanoke, September 1992. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - "The Capital Report" with Rep Costello - Guest: L.F. Payne, 10 September 1992. (Box 83)
  - Videotape -Averett College, Danville, Va. "United We Stand" Forum, L.F. Payne-Bill Hurlburt Debate, 1992. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - The Making of "Sommersby," Charlotte County, 1992. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - Payne for Congress(Fenn & King) "The Label," 1992. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - Payne for Congress (Fenn & King) "The Label" (Two Copies), 1992. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - Payne for Congress (Fenn & King) "Think," 1992. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - Clinton Inauguration Coverage at Monticello, WVIR Charlottesville Channel 29, 17 January 1993. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - Culpeper Baptist Church Worship Service, 17 January 1993. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - Thomas Jefferson 250th Birthday, Monticello, WVIR Charlottesville Channel 29 Coverage, 13 April 1993. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - "Blue Ridge Nightline" with L.F. Payne, Blue Ridge Public TV Roanoke, 15 April 1993. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne on Federal Budget Deficit Legislation, WVIR Charlottesville Channel 29, June 1993. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - Policy Development, Virginia Farm Bureau Federation, July 1993. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne on NAFTA, Roanoke Channel 7, 16 November 1993. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne on 1994 Virginia Senate Primary Battle, Dateline WVIR Charlottesville Channel 29 News, 3 December 1993. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne on Clinton Health Care Plan, WVIR Charlottesville Channel 29, 26 January 1994. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - National Association of Wholesale Distributors - Health Care Panel, 2 February 1994. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - George Landrith to Oppose L.F. Payne, TV29 Noon News, 8 February 1994. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - National Video Conference with First Lady Hillary Rodham Clinton and Gov. Richard F. Celeste, National Health Care Campaign, 19 March 1994. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - Campaign Announcement, 21 April 1994. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - Payne Re-Election Announcement and coverage of death of President Nixon, various local and national news broadcasts, 22 April 1994. and Bill Hurlburt Interview, "Nightline," Blue Ridge Public TV, 1992. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - Payne Announces Run for Re-Election, WSET Lynchburg Channel 13, 22 April 1994. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne on NAFTA/Sperry Marine, Inc. Tour, WVIR Charlottesville Channel 29, 1994. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - George Landrith and LF Payne on Crime Bill, WVIR Charlottesville Channel 29, 1994. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - Martinsville Cable 6 Programming, 1994. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Congress (Strother, Duffy) Compilation Reel 1994. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Congress (Strother, Duffy) Compilation Reel (Four Copies), 1994. (Box 83)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Congress (Strother, Duffy) "Way of Life" (Two Copies), 1994. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Congress (Strother, Duffy) "Seniors," 1994. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Congress (Strother, Duffy) "Bio," 1994. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Congress (Strother, Duffy) "Bio" (Revised), 1994. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Congress (Strother, Duffy) "Sold Out" (Three Copies), 1994. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Congress (Strother, Duffy) "New Contract" (Two Copies), 1994. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Congress (Strother, Duffy) "Bio," "Values 1," "Values 2" (Two Copies), 1994. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Congress (Strother, Duffy) "Way of Life" and "Textile Revised" (Two Copies), 1994. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Congress (Strother, Duffy) "Susan," 1994. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Congress (Strother, Duffy) "Closer," 1994. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne for Congress (Strother, Duffy) ) "Bio," "Textile Jobs," "Health Care," and "Police Talk," 1994. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - Martha Rosales Story (Manuel Perez), Channel 57 Martinsville, 21 July 1995. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - "Tobacco Under Fire," Series,(Five Segments), WDBJ Roanoke Channel 7, 13-17 November 1995. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne on FDA Tobacco Regulations, WDBJ Roanoke Channel 7 News, and WSET Lynchburg Channel 13 News, 1995. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - CBS News, "Eye on America" Tobacco Report. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - L.F. Payne, House Floor, Debt Limit Increase (H.R. 2586), 1995. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - FDA Tobacco Regulations, Various Local and National News Clips, 1995-1996. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - Campaign Announcement, 1996. (Box 84)
  - Videotape - Childs Wintergreen Lawsuit/L.F. Payne Testimony, WDBJ Roanoke Channel 7, September 1997. (Box 84)